Stanford University, Office of Student Activities, Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Additional material, 1978-2004; Accession ARCH.2014-052
  - Volunteer student organization files, 1978-2004
    - Inactive, Stanford, 1978-2004
      - Classical Chinese Dance Troupe, 1999-2001 (Box 13, Folder 9)
      - Stanford Commentary, 1984-1990 (Box 13, Folder 10)
      - Stanford Committees of Correspondence, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 11)
      - Stanford Committee on Law and Human Rights, 1996-1998 (Box 13, Folder 12)
      - Stanford Community Parents' Network, 1997-1999 (Box 13, Folder 13)
      - Stanford Composers Association, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 14)
      - Stanford Concrete Cande Team, 1995-1998 (Box 13, Folder 15)
      - Stanford Court Judges, 1986-2000 (Box 13, Folder 16)
      - Stanford Crisis Pregnancy Network, 1987-1994 (Box 13, Folder 17)
      - Stanford Culinary Club, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 18)
      - Stanford Debate Handbook, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 19)
      - Stanford Democratic Socialists of America, 1979-1991 (Box 13, Folder 20)
      - Stanford Design Group, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 21)
      - Stanford Desis (formerly Stanford Indian Ass'n), 1980-1997 (Box 13, Folder 22)
      - Stanford Dramatic Association, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 23)
      - Stanford EE Interdisciplinary Student Enclave, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 24)
      - Stanford Economics Journal, 1991-1995 (Box 13, Folder 25)
      - Stanford Electronic Gaming Experience, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 26)
      - Stanford Electronic Publishing Project, 1994-1995 (Box 13, Folder 27)
      - Stanford Eng. Club for Automated Manufacturing (SECAM), 1985-2004 (Box 13, Folder 28)
      - Stanford Engineering Student Project Group, 1995-1996 (Box 13, Folder 29)
      - Stanford Entertainment and Sports Law Society, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 30)
      - Stanford Entertainment Network, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 31)
      - Stanford Entrepreneurial Engineers Club, 1986-1989 (Box 13, Folder 32)
      - Stanford Entrepreneurs' Group, 1992-1993 (Box 13, Folder 33)
      - Stanford Environmental Network, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 34)
      - Stanford Field Hockey Club, 1984-1987 (Box 13, Folder 35)
      - Stanford Filipino Organization, 1992-1994 (Box 13, Folder 36)
      - Stanford Flight, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 37)
      - Stanford Flying Club, 1992-1994 (Box 13, Folder 38)
      - Stanford Folkdancers, 1978-1993 (Box 13, Folder 39)
      - Stanford Friends of Tibet, 1991-2001 (Box 13, Folder 40)
      - Stanford Futures Association, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 41)
      - Stanford Gay and Lesbian Policy Forum, 1995-1996 (Box 13, Folder 42)
      - Stanford Gay and Lesbian Counseling Group, 1980-1990 (Box 13, Folder 43)
      - Stanford Glee Club, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 44)
      - Stanford GSB Communications Club, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 45)
      - Stanford GSB Live!, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 46)
      - Stanford GSB Sailing Club, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 47)
      - Stanford Hang Gliding - Aviation Rec., 1983-1990 (Box 13, Folder 48)
      - Student Health Policy Colloquim, 1994-1998 (Box 13, Folder 49)
      - Stanford Health Policy Forum, 1989-1997 (Box 13, Folder 50)
      - Stanford Homelessness Action Coalition (SHAC), 1989-1997 (Box 13, Folder 51)
      - Stanford Heritage Fund, 1983-1984 (Box 13, Folder 52)
      - Stanford Himalayan Club, 1992-1999 (Box 13, Folder 53)
      - Stanford Hong Kong Hi-Tech Association, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 54)
      - Stanford Humanities Review Editorial Collective (SHREC), 1994 (Box 13, Folder 55)
      - Stanford Hybrid Auto Research Project, 1992-1994 (Box 13, Folder 56)
      - Stanford Humanities - SAM, 1992-1998 (Box 13, Folder 57)
      - Stanford Immunology Agency for Students, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 58)
      - Stanford Independent Films, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 59)
      - Stanford India Project, 1991-1992 (Box 13, Folder 60)
      - Stanford Indian Music Group, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 61)
      - Stanford Indigenous and Unrepresented People's Coalition, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 62)
      - Stanford Institute of Industrial Engineers, 1991-2000 (Box 13, Folder 63)
      - Stanford International Development Organziation, 1983-1997 (Box 13, Folder 64)
      - Stanford International Issues Forum, 1991-1992 (Box 13, Folder 65)
      - Stanford Internet Enterprises (SINE), 1998 (Box 13, Folder 66)
      - Stanford Irish Association, 1994-1995 (Box 13, Folder 67)
      - Stanford Investor, 1998-1999 (Box 13, Folder 68)
      - Stanford Jewish Medical Student Association, 1997-2002 (Box 13, Folder 69)
      - Stanford Journal of Health and Science, 1990-1992 (Box 13, Folder 70)
      - Stanford Journal of International Affairs, 1991-1995 (Box 13, Folder 71)
      - Judicial Charter, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 72)
      - Judicial Charter, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 73)
      - Stanford Journal of Law, Business and Finance, 1993-1997 (Box 13, Folder 74)
      - Stanford Karate Club, 1978-1987 (Box 13, Folder 75)
      - Stanford Kendo Club A Branch of the Palo Alto Kendo Dojo, 1996-1999 (Box 13, Folder 76)
      - Stanford Kuk Won, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 77)
      - Stanford Kung Fu Club, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 78)
      - Stanford Law and Policy Review, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 79)
      - Stanford LaKota Oyate, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 80)
      - Stanford Latin Student Alliance (SalSA), 1987-1989 (Box 13, Folder 81)
      - Stanford Law Dance Alliance, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 82)
      - Stanford Law Forum, 1984-1985 (Box 13, Folder 83)
      - Stanford Law and Technology Conference, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 84)
      - Stanford Law Journal, 1981-1995 (Box 13, Folder 85)
      - Stanford Law Partners Association, 1997-1999 (Box 13, Folder 86)
      - Stanford Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual Speakers Bureau, 1988-1993 (Box 13, Folder 87)
      - Stanford Libertarians, 1978-2001 (Box 13, Folder 88)
      - Stanfor Light Opera Workshop, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 89)
      - Stanford Literacy Experiment, 1997-1998 (Box 13, Folder 90)
      - Stanford Magazine for Science, Technology and Research, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 91)
      - Stanford Massage Club, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 92)
      - Stanford Men's Collective, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 93)
      - Stanford Men's Field Hockey Club, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 94)
      - Stanford Medieval Club, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 95)
      - Stanford Medical Committee for Fritrea (SMACE), 1989-1991 (Box 13, Folder 96)
      - Stanford Medical Humanities Group, 1995-1996 (Box 13, Folder 97)
      - Stanford Undergraduate Medical Interpreters, 2001-2002 (Box 13, Folder 98)
      - Stanford Medicine in Local Education (SMILE), 1995-1998 (Box 13, Folder 99)
      - Stanford Med. School Clinical Journal, 1997-2000 (Box 13, Folder 100)
      - Stanford Medical Youth Science Program, 1990-1995 (Box 13, Folder 101)
      - Stanford Media and Medicine Interest Group, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 102)
      - Stanford Medical Review Association, 1998-1999 (Box 13, Folder 103)
      - Stanford Medical Students for a Women's Health Specialty, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 104)
      - Stanford Med 2000 Fund, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 105)
      - Stanford Med. Students-1st Yr. Celeb., 1995 (Box 13, Folder 106)
      - POSUMS -- Stanford Medical Students with Partners and Families, 1999-2001 (Box 13, Folder 107)
      - Stanford Middle East Action Committee, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 108)
      - Stanford Mindfulness Meditation Group, 1993-1994 (Box 13, Folder 109)
      - Stanford Middle East Focus, 1992-1995 (Box 14, Folder 1)
      - Stanford Miles to Go..., 1996-1999 (Box 14, Folder 2)
      - Stanford Mock Trial, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 3)
      - Stanford Model Arab League, 1991, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 4)
      - Stanford Multimedia Group, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 5)
      - Stanford Moscow Exchange Program, 1992-1995 (Box 14, Folder 6)
      - Stanford Music Video Association, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 7)
      - Stanford Native Parent Community, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 8)
      - Student National Medical Association (SNMA), 1994 (Box 14, Folder 9)
      - Stanford Names Project Quilt Display Committee, 1994-1995 (Box 14, Folder 10)
      - Stanford Native American Arts and Crafts Organization, 1988, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 11)
      - Stanford Native American Pow-Wow Society, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 12)
      - Stanford University National Organization for Women, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 13)
      - Stanford Network of Outreach Development, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 14)
      - Stanford Objectivists, 1985-1992 (Box 14, Folder 15)
      - Stanford Outreach and Academic Reinforcement, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 16)
      - Stanford Organization for the Mentally Disabled, 1992-1995 (Box 14, Folder 17)
      - Stanford Papua New Guinea Medical Group, 1997-2001 (Box 14, Folder 18)
      - Stanford Paintball, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 19)
      - Stanford/Palo Alto Users Group for PCs, 1983-1991 (Box 14, Folder 20)
      - Stanford Panza Española, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 21)
      - Stanford Performance Arts Network, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 22)
      - Stanford Policy Institute, 1992-1993 (Box 14, Folder 23)
      - Stanford Political Quarterly, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 24)
      - Stanford Political Union, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 25)
      - Stanford Pro-Choice Alliance, 1989-1993 (Box 14, Folder 26)
      - Stanford Product Design Group, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 27)
      - Stanford Project on National Service, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 28)
      - Stanford Project for Accelerated Reading in Kids, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 29)
      - Stanford Raimondi Technique Volunteers, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 30)
      - Stanford Squash Women's Intercollegiate Team, 2001-2002 (Box 14, Folder 31)
      - Stanford Quarterly, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 32)
      - Stanford Red Hoop Players, 1993-1994 (Box 14, Folder 33)
      - Stanford Robotics Team, 1997-1998 (Box 14, Folder 34)
      - Stanford Reform Party, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 35)
      - Stanford Returning Students Association, 2000-2001 (Box 14, Folder 36)
      - Stanford Rock for Choice, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 37)
      - Stanford Rodeo Club, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 38)
      - Stanford Rugby Club, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 39)
      - Stanford Russian Club, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 40)
      - Stanford Salsa Club, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 41)
      - Stanford Scuba Club, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 42)
      - Stanford Russian Chamber Choir, 1992-1997 (Box 14, Folder 43)
      - Stanford Sadomusicism, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 44)
      - Stanford Safe Transportation Program, 1987-1998 (Box 14, Folder 45)
      - Stanford University Shorinji Kempo Club, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 46)
      - Stanford Shorin-Ryu Karate, 1987-2001 (Box 14, Folder 47)
      - Stanford Samulnori, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 48)
      - Stanford Society for International Studies, 1999-2002 (Box 14, Folder 49)
      - Stanford Sailing Association, 1989-1997 (Box 14, Folder 50)
      - Stanford Sierra Club, 1989-1990 (Box 14, Folder 51)
      - Stanford Skateboard Club, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 52)
      - Stanford Soccer Club, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 53)
      - Stanford Society of Automotive Engineers, 1998-1999 (Box 14, Folder 54)
      - Stanford Socialist Club, 1990-1992 (Box 14, Folder 55)
      - Stanford Society of Performing Arts (SSPA), 1990-1994 (Box 14, Folder 56)
      - Stanford Software Developers' Network (DevNet), 1996-1998 (Box 14, Folder 57)
      - Stanford-Soviet Exchange Project, 1987-1991 (Box 14, Folder 58)
      - Stanford Speech and Debate Society, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 59)
      - Stanford Speakers Foundation, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 60)
      - Stanford Stargazers, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 61)
      - Stanford University Steel Bridge Team, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 62)
      - Stanford Straight But Not Narrow, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 63)
      - Stanford Student Alumni Network (STAN), 1981-1999 (Box 14, Folder 64)
      - Stanford Student Committee of Volunteers in Asia, 1990-1991 (Box 14, Folder 65)
      - Stanford Student Computer and Network Privacy Project, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 66)
      - Stanford Students Against Gun Violence, 1999-2000 (Box 14, Folder 67)
      - Stanford Students for Anarchy, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 68)
      - Stanford Students in AFROTC, 1973-1994 (Box 14, Folder 69)
      - Stanford Students for Individual Liberty, 1991-1993 (Box 14, Folder 70)
      - Stanford Students for International Awareness, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 71)
      - Stanford Students for Judaism and Social Justice, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 72)
      - Stanford Students for Peace, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 73)
      - Stanford Students for Perot, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 74)
      - Stanford Students for Deaf Awareness, 1983-1992 (Box 14, Folder 75)
      - Stanford Students for Prisoners' Rights, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 76)
      - Stanford Student Pugwash, 1994-2001 (Box 14, Folder 77)
      - Stanford Students Supporting Sklyarov, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 78)
      - Stanford Student Television, 1986-1998 (Box 14, Folder 79)
      - Stanford Surf and Turf Association, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 80)
      - Stanford Surf Team, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 81)
      - Stanford Surfing Club, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 82)
      - Stanford Symphonic Band, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 83)
      - Stanford Synchronized Swim Club, 1978-1992 (Box 14, Folder 84)
      - Stanford Trampoline Club, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 85)
      - Stanford Symphonic Chorus, 1992-1995 (Box 14, Folder 86)
      - Stanford Tang Soo Do, 1991-1993 (Box 14, Folder 87)
      - Stanford Students to Elect Jerry Brown, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 88)
      - Stanford Teach-Out on the Persian Gulf, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 89)
      - Stanford Technology Management Society (STEMS), 1992-1996 (Box 14, Folder 90)
      - Stanford Transcendental Meditation Club, 1978-1993 (Box 14, Folder 91)
      - Stanford Traditionist Organization, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 92)
      - Stanford Undergraduate Business Association, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 93)
      - Stanford Undergraduate Biologists, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 94)
      - Stanford Undergraduates in Education, 1992-1993 (Box 14, Folder 95)
      - Stanford Undergraduate Historical Society, 1984-1986 (Box 14, Folder 96)
      - Stanford University Golf Association, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 97)
      - Stanford University Harmonica Society, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 98)
      - Stanford Undergrad Parent and Non-Trad Student Network, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 99)
      - Stanford Underwater Diving Sports, 1986-1988 (Box 14, Folder 100)
      - Stanford Union of Public Affairs Organizations, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 101)
      - Stanford Unified Co-Op Council, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 102)
      - Stanford United for Rape Elimination (SURE), 1986-1999 (Box 14, Folder 103)
      - Stanford Unity Organizing Committee, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 104)
      - Stanford University 4-H Club, 1991-1993 (Box 14, Folder 105)
      - Stanford University Croquet Club, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 106)
      - Stanford University Big Siblings (SUBS), 1998 (Box 14, Folder 107)
      - Stanford University Manufacturing Conference, 1991-1995 (Box 14, Folder 108)
      - Stanford University Pocket Billiards Society, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 109)
      - Stanford University Stu-Ryu Jiu-Jitsu, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 110)
      - Stanford University Issues Forum (SUNIF), 1997 (Box 14, Folder 111)
      - Stanford University Transcendental Meditation Club, 1996-2000 (Box 14, Folder 112)
      - Stanford University Undergraduate Law Society, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 113)
      - Stanford Volunteer Network, 1984-1996 (Box 14, Folder 114)
      - Stanford Vegetarians, 1987-1991 (Box 14, Folder 115)
      - Stanford Women's Center, 1978-1983 (Box 14, Folder 116)
      - Stanford Weightlifting Club, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 117)
      - Stanford Water Environment Federation, 1998-1999 (Box 14, Folder 118)
      - Stanford Women's Water Polo, 1979-1994 (Box 14, Folder 119)
      - Stanford Women's Speakers Organization, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 120)
      - Stanford White Crane Silat, 1987-1993 (Box 14, Folder 121)
      - Stanford Women in Medicine, 1983-1998 (Box 14, Folder 122)
      - Stanford Workshop on Political and Social Issues (SWOPSI), 1992 (Box 14, Folder 123)
      - Club Women's Lacrosse, 1980-1993 (Box 14, Folder 124)
      - Stanford Women's Softball Team, 1980-1990 (Box 14, Folder 125)
      - Stanford Women's Field Hockey, 1990-1991 (Box 14, Folder 126)
      - Stanford Xiang Qi Chinese Chess, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 127)
      - Stanford Volunteers for Health, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 128)
      - Stanford Yoga Society, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 129)
    - Rejected Volunteer Student Organizations, 1978-2004 (Box 15)
  - Fraternal organization and house government files, 1978-2004
    - Active, 1978-2004 (Box 15-16)
      - Inter-Sorority Council- registrations, 1980-2003 (Box 15, Folder 36)
      - Alpha Kappa Alpha, 1991-2002 (Box 15, Folder 37)
      - Alpha Kappa Delta Phi, 1999-2002 (Box 15, Folder 38)
      - African American Fraternal Association (AAFSA), 1991-2002 (Box 15, Folder 39)
      - Alpha Epsilon Pi, 1995-2002 (Box 15, Folder 40)
      - Alpha Kappa Psi Coed Professional Business Fraternity, 1999-2003 (Box 15, Folder 41)
      - Chi Omega, 1990-2002 (Box 15, Folder 42)
      - Delta Delta Delta, 1999-2002 (Box 15, Folder 43)
      - Delta Delta Delta, 1991-2004 (Box 15, Folder 44)
      - Delta Sigma Theta, 1991-2003 (Box 15, Folder 45)
      - Delta Kappa Epsilon, 1973-2003 (Box 15, Folder 46)
      - Delta Tau Delta, 1997-2003 (Box 15, Folder 47)
      - Colony of Gamma Zeta Alpha Fraternity, 2000-2002 (Box 15, Folder 48)
      - Kappa Alpha Order (Mud Volleyball), 1992-1997 (Box 16, Folder 1)
      - Kappa Alpha Theta, 1993-23 (Box 16, Folder 2)
      - Kappa Kappa Gamma, 1981-2004 (Box 16, Folder 3)
      - Kappa Alpha Order, 1996-2003 (Box 16, Folder 4)
      - Kappa Alpha Psi, 1998-2003 (Box 16, Folder 5)
      - Kappa Sigma, 1995-2002 (Box 16, Folder 6)
      - Lamda Phi Epsilon, 1997-2003 (Box 16, Folder 7)
      - Phi Kappa Psi, 1998-2002 (Box 16, Folder 8)
      - Sigma Alpha Epsilon, 1995-2003 (Box 16, Folder 9)
      - Sigma Chi, 1998-2002 (Box 16, Folder 10)
      - Sigma Nu, 1999-2003 (Box 16, Folder 11)
      - Sigma Phi Epsilon Housing Application, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 12)
      - Sigma Phi Epsilon, 1992-2002 (Box 16, Folder 13)
      - Pi Beta Phi Sorority, 1991-2003 (Box 16, Folder 14)
      - Sigma Theta Psi, 2001-2003 (Box 16, Folder 15)
      - Theta Delta Chi, 1996-2003 (Box 16, Folder 16)
      - Theta Xi, 1997-2002 (Box 16, Folder 17)
      - 592 Mayfield, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 18)
      - Adams House, 1997-2001 (Box 16, Folder 19)
      - Alondra, 1993-2003 (Box 16, Folder 20)
      - Cedro, 1993-2001 (Box 16, Folder 31)
      - Durand, 1994-2001 (Box 16, Folder 32)
      - East House, 1992-2002 (Box 16, Folder 33)
      - Enchanted Broccoli Forest, 1993-2002 (Box 16, Folder 34)
      - Escondido Village Undergraduate Residents, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 35)
      - Faisan House, 1992-2002 (Box 16, Folder 36)
      - Hammarskjold, 1993-2001 (Box 16, Folder 37)
      - Haus Mitteleuropa, 1992-2001 (Box 16, Folder 38)
      - Kairos, 2000-2001 (Box 16, Folder 39)
      - Lamda Nu, 1992-2001 (Box 16, Folder 40)
      - Lantana House, 1992-2001 (Box 16, Folder 41)
      - Loro, 1997-2001 (Box 16, Folder 42)
      - Murray House, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 43)
      - Muweka-Tah-Ruk House, 1992-2002 (Box 16, Folder 44)
      - Okada, 1992-2002 (Box 16, Folder 45)
      - Potter House, 1994-2002 (Box 16, Folder 46)
      - Robert Moore House South-American Studies, 1992-2001 (Box 16, Folder 47)
      - Schiff, 1995-2001 (Box 16, Folder 48)
      - Serra House, 1993-2002 (Box 16, Folder 49)
      - Yost House, 1994-2001 (Box 16, Folder 50)
      - Xanadu House, 1992-2001 (Box 16, Folder 51)
      - Stanford Chaparral The Humor Magazine, 2008 Feb. 18 (Box 16, Folder 52)
      - Various Teaching Position Ads., undated (Box 16, Folder 53)
      - Storey House, 1992-2002 (Box 16, Folder 54)
      - Grove Houses, 1993-2000 (Box 16, Folder 55)
      - Larkin, 1992-1999 (Box 16, Folder 56)
      - Beta Theta Pi Kitchen, 1994-1995 (Box 16, Folder 57)
      - Stanford Chapparal The Humor Magazine, 2008 Feb. 18 (Box 16, Folder 58)
    - Inactive, 1978-2004 (Box 16)
      - American Studies (Murray House), 1998-1999 (Box 16, Folder 70)
      - Adelfa House, 1992-1997 (Box 16, Folder 71)
      - ATO - Alpha Tau Omicron, 1992-1994 (Box 16, Folder 72)
      - (ATO) Alpha Ta Omicron, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 73)
      - Alpha Sigma House, 1995-1996 (Box 16, Folder 74)
      - Burbank, 1993-2000 (Box 16, Folder 75)
      - Chi Theta Chi, 1992-2000 (Box 16, Folder 76)
      - Castano, 1997-2001 (Box 16, Folder 77)
      - Clifford, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 78)
      - Columbae House, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 79)
      - Columbae, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 80)
      - 717 Delores, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 81)
      - Donner House, 1993-2000 (Box 16, Folder 82)
      - Eucalipto, 1993-1998 (Box 16, Folder 83)
      - Gavilan, 1993-2001 (Box 16, Folder 84)
      - Granada, 1994-1997 (Box 16, Folder 85)
      - La Casa Italiana, 1993-1997 (Box 16, Folder 86)
      - The French House (La Maison Francaise), 1992-1999 (Box 16, Folder 87)
      - 675 Lomita House, 1993-1994 (Box 16, Folder 88)
      - Madera House, 1992-1993 (Box 16, Folder 89)
      - 553 Mayfield, 1992-2000 (Box 16, Folder 90)
      - 557 Mayfield, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 91)
      - Mirlo, 1993-1999 (Box 16, Folder 92)
      - Mirrielees House, 1993-1998 (Box 16, Folder 93)
      - Robinson House, 1995-1998 (Box 16, Folder 94)
      - Roble Hall, 1992-1998 (Box 16, Folder 95)
      - Synergy House, 1992-1995 (Box 16, Folder 96)
      - Terra House, 1994-1999 (Box 16, Folder 97)
      - Twain, 1995-1998 (Box 16, Folder 98)
      - Whitman House, 1992-1998 (Box 16, Folder 99)
      - Zeta Alpha Pi House, 1992-1997 (Box 16, Folder 100)